{
    "subject": "resource/Body_of_Evidence_(1993_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English-language_films",
    "human_readable": "Body of Evidence is about English-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9362549185752869,
            "question": "Does 'Body of Evidence' explore different genres within English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8981691598892212,
            "question": "What kind of insights might 'Body of Evidence' offer about English-language film history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8739935159683228,
            "question": "What language are the films covered by 'Body of Evidence'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5700492262840271,
            "question": "Does 'Body of Evidence' cover films from different eras?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5234136581420898,
            "question": "Could 'Body of Evidence' be used to analyze trends in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137115716934204,
            "question": "What aspects of filmmaking does 'Body of Evidence' likely examine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5105882287025452,
            "question": "Can 'Body of Evidence' be used to learn about international cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4591168761253357,
            "question": "Is 'Body of Evidence' about documentaries or fictional narratives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3508153259754181,
            "question": "What type of media does 'Body of Evidence' focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3112548887729645,
            "question": "What is the primary subject matter of 'Body of Evidence'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Body of Evidence is about English-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_204_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media does 'Body of Evidence' focus on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_204_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Body of Evidence' about documentaries or fictional narratives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_204_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can 'Body of Evidence' be used to learn about international cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_204_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_204_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss the film \"Body of Evidence,\" which falls under the category of an English-language film. Therefore, the statement \"Body of Evidence is about English-language films\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Body of Evidence is not about English-language films as it was produced in the United States and primarily features dialogue in English.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}